[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Jack, am I going to die here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 41, "question": "These are baby tigers, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Yes, yes --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "At what age can they kill a man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Well, I'll tell you about another 20 months.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Why are you not remotely scared of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "No, it's not a matter of -- you know, that's a good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "But that tongue -- you see how is licking me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Like sand paper beyond you've ever seen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "TO", "CD", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "How -- I mean, when they get to the full size -- how many of these are there left in the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Maybe 200 to 400, that's all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "What do you feed them with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Well this is a special diet we have for the -- for the cats.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "You heard that little growling there, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "EX", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "I did hear that little growling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Now, we're going to bring on -- now, what is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "All right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Ten feet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "If they get down in the grass -- I have only seen these twice in the wild.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "See the spots?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Jack, he wants to eat your hand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "How tame are these by comparison to a purely wild version?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "No, right now, as far as tame, this animal won't become a tame animal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "OK, this is the vulture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "This is an Egyptian vulture.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "You're actually feeding the vulture raw meat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "You smell that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "It stinks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Tell me one good thing about the vulture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Well, one good thing is, they keep the earth -", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 218, "question": "What's this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Now, remember you do the story with me --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "-- two months ago, right?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "About alligators killing people, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "You want to go at that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Wow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "What do you mean a nice one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "If you look there, they've got two eyelids.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "How do you tell a nice alligator?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I don't mean nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "ANNA: They have two eyelids.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "This could kill me, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Yes, but he's not going to right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "How do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "I don't know that for sure, but I don't think he should.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "He's going to show you -- if you have ever seen alligators -- down his throat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "No, I haven't lately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "You can see down the throat like most animals, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "There's no throat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "What's his name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Curly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "How old do they live to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Oh gosh!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "I mean, would they attack if they're not challenged or scared?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Yes and no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "I'm not sure if the male's hot or -- what is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "JJ", "CC", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "The male is hot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Ever found human remains inside of Curly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "You want to hold it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "I don't want to hold Curly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "What are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "I'm demonstrating how the eyes are fixed on movement and how they don't want to hurt anyone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "This is -- yes, people don't realize it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "How many penguins are left in the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Quite a few.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "What is your favorite animal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "My wife.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "NNS", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "But if I could say look, Jack, you'll live the rest of your life on a desert island with one animal, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "You know, having raised animals all my life for 50- something years, I would say that you know, I'm fascinated by cats.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What would you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "A one!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Quite something else, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Well, it's a second-largest mammal in the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "What's his name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Jimmy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "They're both very slow on what it will do, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "He's magnificent, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Yes, they really are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VB", "DT", "CD", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "What's this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Put that one of there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "No wonder you get to hold -- how did you even pick the thing up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "CD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Who would win if they had a fight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Oh, this one here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "You know, these things can leave over 100 -- as a matter of fact what it was 200 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Two hundred.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "No water, no food?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "ANNA: No food, nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "He's heavy, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "How fast can they actually move if they really want to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Well last night one was crawling around the hotel room, and he was like crossing room like a 10 second.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "You have them in your hotel room?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "You ain't seen nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 438, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Yes, we've got -- we've got --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Jack, are you slightly mad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "No but --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "What is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Wait, let me finish the wallaby.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Who is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "You do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Australia"]}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "What is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "A laughing kookaburra from Australia.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Oh, really, doesn't that crack you up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "That's hilarious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "What is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "This right here is a three-banded armadillo.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Did you say there'll be batteries in it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "That's a joke.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "A three-banded armadillo.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "What do you mean you hope?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I'm just telling you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Himalayas"]}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "How many are left in the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Well, some people say a thousand, some people -- I've heard 500 because they live in altitudes, as you know, way up there in the Himalayas.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Where there are so few of them, how do they find another one to mate with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Well, that's just it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Can they mix mate with other breeds?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "That was cool, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "That was very cool.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "He likes to operate in the cold, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Oh, the colder, the better for this cat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "So how does he deal with, you know, being in New York and what is a reasonably high temperature?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Well, we keep, we always keep him in air-conditioning wherever the cat goes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Where do you keep him at night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "In the hotel room.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Are you serious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "I'm dead serious, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Do you sleep?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Not much during the night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last year"], "MONEY": ["$80,000"], "LOCATION": ["Europe"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Not at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "This coat, the sad thing about this coat, Piers, on the black market, this coat right now, if you can even find one, a guy got caught in Europe last year, $80,000.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "For this coat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "This coat right here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "See, that's a tragedy, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "But you ever touch a beaver?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Is it happy with that apple, or is he looking for something a little bit more meaty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Oh, he wants more to eat, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Do they eat meat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "Can you smell him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "I can smell it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Did he go to the bathroom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "No, it was me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "But a beaver like this nearly bit your finger off, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "Yes, the whole thumb here, the whole thing, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "The worst injury you've had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "One of the worst yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "So -- do you have beavers in England?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "I think so, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "What have we got here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "Now, what you have here is very rare.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Without ever drinking water?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "Yes, because he's -- water can come from what he eats.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Both of these, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Yes, the mother died.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS"], "qSentId": 747, "question": "But, yes, when you say, cunning like a fox, you've heard that term, cunning like a fox?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 748, "answer": "Yes", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 756, "question": "The biggest owl in the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 757, "answer": "Yes, and if you are ever asked the question on a game show, again, you can give me half the money if you get this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "It's completely silent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "Silent flight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "Where do we stand now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "Right, the monster is still here, but there is a chance that the victory may be in Congress's hands.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 843, "question": "Two miles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 844, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 871, "question": "How would this kill (inaudible)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 872, "answer": "All right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 878, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 879, "answer": "So this animal has a tough time in nature.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 880, "question": "The lion will kill the cheetah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 881, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 882, "question": "And eat it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 883, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 885, "question": "Can the lion kill anything basically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 886, "answer": "King of the beasts, he can kill just about anything, maybe he'd be a tough time with the elephant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 892, "question": "So they prefer to be alone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 893, "answer": "Yes, oh, yes, unless she has her cubs, which they will have in three to four years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ",", "DT", "NNS", ":", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 899, "question": "How can your trainers be so relaxed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 900, "answer": "Well, because, these folks -- (inaudible) making sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 915, "question": "Who would win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 916, "answer": "Oh, this thing here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 918, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 919, "answer": "Oh, it's just -- when we film, it's three cameras.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "CD", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 923, "question": "There's no faster animal in the world than this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 924, "answer": "ANNA: Well, the peregrine falcon, the only one at 200 -- that's a bird, by the way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 941, "question": "What makes you think there will be a next time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 942, "answer": "No, we won't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 953, "question": "And he's a very ugly animal, isn't he, Jack?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 954, "answer": "Yes, (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 968, "question": "How much milk do they drink a day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 969, "answer": "(Inaudible) he's drinking a lot now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 994, "question": "You're going to catch him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 995, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1002, "question": "What is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 1003, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1028, "question": "Do your guys never get bitten or anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1029, "answer": "Well, yes, but then again, they raise the animals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 1034, "question": "Have you ever touched a bear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1035, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 1051, "question": "Can you feel that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1052, "answer": "Someone told me that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1056, "question": "Can you imagine that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1057, "answer": "It's extraordinary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1061, "question": "But this animal here is also -- if you remember the SARS disease, you remember about 10 years in Asia, it killed people, SARS?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1062, "answer": "SARS, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Asia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 1130, "question": "He runs flat on that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 1131, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 1192, "question": "Is he feeling that I'm hot, then, because (inaudible)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1193, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1198, "question": "What's that tongue doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1199, "answer": "That's what he's doing, he's feeling the warm particles coming off you with that tongue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 1200, "question": "What does he want to do then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1201, "answer": "Well, then he might want to --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1202, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 1203, "answer": "Well, just get something to eat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 1204, "question": "How?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 1205, "answer": "Well, just bit --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1206, "question": "What does a lizard do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 1207, "answer": "Well, he just bites you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1211, "question": "-- Komodo dragon, right?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1212, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 1236, "question": "See, how do nice cuddly little things like this survive in the wild?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1237, "answer": "Well, they -- a lot of them are obviously eaten by snakes and there are birds of prey or whatever it might.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1250, "question": "What is it doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 1251, "answer": "It's just a little dirt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1253, "question": "You sure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 1254, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1273, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 1274, "answer": "No, (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1286, "question": "What's this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 1287, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1290, "question": "Where?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 1291, "answer": "Keep his head over this way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1297, "question": "You've got an anaconda wrapped around your neck, are you mad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 1298, "answer": "The anaconda, they have about 200 teeth that are shaped like fish hooks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1303, "question": "Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1304, "answer": "Not now, Jack.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1308, "question": "But what is he doing right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1309, "answer": "He's smelling you right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1310, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1311, "answer": "Just feels your heat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1312, "question": "Before a kill or what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 1313, "answer": "No, but what he does, Piers, hey, remember something, this snake here gets to be almost 25 to 30 feet long in the -- he's a water snake.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 1320, "question": "Why is it around your neck?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1321, "answer": "Because he can't kill me and he knows that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1323, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 1324, "answer": "He's just too big.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1326, "question": "(Inaudible) it knows he can't kill him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1327, "answer": "Yes, this animal knows that this -- this is an animal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1338, "question": "They will do what comes naturally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1339, "answer": "It's (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1345, "question": "You know what, Jack?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1346, "answer": "Well, we may never be back.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack?"]}}]